Claude Co-work is one of the best ways
to supercharge your real estate business
and automate time sucking tasks, but
unfortunately most agents don't know how
to properly do it. So, I'm going to walk
you through step by step, click byclick,
exactly not only how to understand
Claude Co-work as a real estate agent,
but also in this example, I'm going to
show you how to build an AI powered
content assistant that would replace a
virtual assistant and a social media
content manager using these six blocks.
So, what are we going to be building?
Well, the first is going to be a realtor
business profile. Claude needs to
understand your market, your target
avatar, and your goals. Then we're going
to build out a workspace to keep
everything organized so that it's easy
to find, navigate, and use. Then we're
going to give it instructions. I'm going
to give you the exact prompt that you
can copy and paste. I'll show you how to
get it for free so that every time you
want to do something, it does it the
right way the first time immediately.
Same [snorts] with the right skills. I'm
also going to show you how to connect it
to a Google Drive folder so that every
time you ask for your new content
strategy, it's going to put it in the
same place. But the most important part
is at the end of this video, I'm going
to show you how to create a weekly
automated content task so that every
single week, it automatically delivers
you the exact videos you should record
that week specific to your business,
your goals, and generating the kind of
leads that you want. So, let's go ahead
and dive in. Now, the first thing that
we need to do looking at Claude is
making sure that you've downloaded the
desktop app. That's going to be the only
way that you get access to Claude
Co-work. So, you can go to claude.com/d
download. I'll link that in the
description so you can click it as well.
But you have to be on the desktop app
and you have to be on the $20 a month
plan, the pro plan as you'll be able to
see down here in order to make sure that
you have access to Claude Co-work as
well for productivity. So after you've
downloaded the desktop, that's where we
can see here. Normally you just have
access to chat, but when you do the $23
a month, you have access to co-work.
What is the difference before we start
diving into how to use this? When you
have a chat, it goes back and forth with
you in a chat very linearly and it's
conversational in order to go back and
forth and back and forth using the
information it has access to on the
internet in order to give you a
response. With co-work, I want you to
view this as your automated assistant.
That's where it can actually do tasks
for you. We can connect it, which we
will, to our email, our calendar, our
Google Drive. It can use all of your
information about your business to
deliver it the right way that you want.
So, think of chat as back and forth
conversation. Think of co-work as an
assistant doing the work for you. So,
now let's go ahead and get started with
context. So, the first thing that we
need to do is give context to Claude as
to who you are. What are you trying to
do? What is your goal with your content
so that it understands your business?
So, what I'm going to do here is just
paste in this prompt. I'm an awesome
real estate agent. I work with
relocation buyers specializing in new
construction.
And this is something that you could
just do in a chat.
So, we're going to go ahead and just get
started.
Now, what I want you to understand with
this is that this is going to be
something very basic. If you want to do
this the utmost powerful way, that's
where I've built out an entire free
clawed course showing you how to
automate your entire real estate
business. Most people are charging like
$5,000 to teach you this stuff. It's
entirely free. I built this out for you.
And as you can see here, we actually
gave custom skills to build your brain
for you in Claude. Also, how to reverse
engineer your goals so Claude
understands your business of what you're
looking to achieve. Then we build out
your entire personal brand and replace a
virtual assistant and a content engine,
but most importantly, lead magnets and
funnels. It's all entirely free. And if
you want access to it, just drop a
comment below and let me know what your
favorite part of this video is so that I
can learn a bit more about you as well
as like the video. If you do those two
things, I will make sure to give you the
free course. So, coming back to Claude,
we can come down here and say that,
okay,
it's done some research and here's the
document, right? So this is going to be
you and you can download it as an MD
file which is exactly what you want to
do. So an MD file is just a markdown
file. This is a type of file that Claude
likes to be used when it comes to
uploading files into the project which
is going to be the next component of it.
So the next thing that we need to do is
we need to build the actual workspace.
Where is your content manager going to
live? that's going to be in a project.
So, as you can see here, you can have a
project for a virtual assistant. I have
one for my YouTube channel just to give
you some context where it has
instructions. This is how I want my
content for my YouTube channel to be
delivered every time to me. So, now
Claude knows how I like to work. It also
has all my files, information about me,
my target avatar, all of this which are
the context files. So for you, let's go
do the same new project and we will just
say YouTube assistant
done.
And now what we're going to do is we're
going to upload your instructions as
well.
So I will copy and paste this here.
You're my real estate content assistant.
Your job is to help me create simple,
clear, local lead generating content for
my business. Always write in a way
that's easy for buyers to understand.
Avoid complex jargon, which is the worst
thing you can do. Focus on content that
builds trust, positions me as a local
expert, and generates conversation with
clients when giving me ideas. Include
practical topics that you can film. So,
now we've got our instructions, but we
can also add the context file, which we
just created. So I'll upload my open my
documents and this is the file we just
downloaded the markdown file. So now it
understands us which is going to be the
second component of this.
So now we've got our assistant, we've
got a project, we've got instructions
and it has context about us.
Now, what we need to do is we need to
build a skill. And I want you to build a
skill because the worst thing that you
could do is waste time with AI. The goal
is for it to save time. So, where most
agents go wrong is every time they need
a video, they go into Claude and they
write something like, "I need a list of
videos for this month." Well, then it
gives you videos, but you don't like it.
It doesn't have the script. It doesn't
have the description. It doesn't have
titles. It doesn't have the hook. It
doesn't have the call to action. So, you
have to go back and forth in the chat
and ask it for all these things every
single time. But if we just build a
skill, a skill is a reusable process
Claude can follow again and again. So,
if we build a skill for this, you save
the process once and you reuse it for
Instagram real scripts, YouTube content
ideas. So, it's a repeatable process
that saves you time. Think of it as an
SOP or a standard operating procedure
for a certain activity that you're going
to do on an ongoing basis. So, let's go
ahead and create one. Now, [snorts]
there's multiple ways to access skills.
If you want to see all of my skills, we
can come over to co-work here and you
come down over to skills. And now you
can see I've got a lot of skills, right?
Canva assistant. So, being able to
automate all of your Instagram
carousels, competition analysis, we can
look at daily planners. If we come down
here, open house, pre-listing,
newsletters.
We can look at personal brand persona,
brand guides, logo designs, market
updates, neighborhood tours, script
writers, YouTube channel setup, YouTube
repurposing. And by the way, if you want
all of those skills, we built out 40 of
them for you so that you can immediately
download them. And these are all based
on what my team uses. Again, that's in
the free course if you access it. So
coming back to this,
we got to build a skill. So these are
the skills that I have. But if you want
to access skills, you can come over to
customize
and then come down under customize and
you're automatically going to be
defaulted to skills. Now if you download
the ones that I have, you could populate
them here or you can add a skill. Now
there's two different ways to create a
skill. First, you can either just click
create with Claude and it will open a
new chat and you can create the skill or
you can literally come in here and ask
for it. So, let me show you what this
looks like.
I will copy this and I will paste this.
Create a custom clawed skill, right?
Specifically calling out what you want
called the real estate YouTube topic
planner. This skill should help me,
right? You can just put me.
Uh, generate YouTube topics and video
topics about your market. Follow the
8020 content strategy. 80% proven
topics, 20% niche. Avoid repetitive
topics. Explain why it's worth creating
and working Claude co-work. So, we're
going to go ahead and we're going to
create that.
So now as you can see here it's going to
get working on all of this in order to
create this skill for us. So we can see
here progress build real estate YouTube
topic planner skill package it as a zip
folder verify it and deliver it because
when we want to upload this skill it
needs to be in that proper zip folder.
As you can see here, it's going through
the process, writing the file, and it's
going to use the skills creator to do
so. So, now it's building up the skill,
and now every single time we need
YouTube video topics, it's going to know
exactly what we need for those topics.
Now, the skills that I have for you in
that course, um, they will take care of
the SEO, they will take care of the
scripting, they will take care of
literally everything. This is just a
quick tutorial basically to show you how
you can get the right video topic ideas
anytime that you want. So, I'll wait for
this to finish and I'll show you what it
looks like. Okay. So, as you can see
here, it is complete. And it says that,
okay, the skills ready, and it's going
to walk through gathering all of your
video topics, ranking by buyer and
seller intent, making your weekly plan,
and now we need to upload the zip into
Claude and install it, and it'll trigger
things like what should you film or
YouTube topics without needing the exact
skill name. So, we can just say allow.
And now we've got that here, which is
our skill. So what I'm going to do is
I'm going to come back to the project
and we can go customize skills and we
need to add. So now what we need to do
is upload a skill and all that you need
to do is drag and drop the folder here
rather.
So if you come you'll see this the skill
MD it downloaded as this file skill MD.
So all that we need to do is drag and
drop that in there. And now you can see
the real estate YouTube topic planner is
here.
And now you can see it's on. We need to
make sure that this is on. And what the
skill does, it turns four outputs,
market, audience, business goals, and
video history into a weekly batch of
content. Gathers four outputs, market,
ideal audience, business goals, and
previous video library. Checks for
repeats so you don't repetitively do it.
Applies the 8020 topic strategy.
and then prioritizes intent not novelty
produces your weekly content plan
anytime you want. So this skill is ready
to go and now we have access to that
skill the weekly YouTube content
planner.
Now if we come over here,
we can either search the skill there or
we can do weekly YouTube
as we can see here and we come down and
we've got our YouTube content planner.
Right there we go. So we can use that
skill anytime that we want. Now, before
going to the next layer, because I'm
going to show you how to create a
scheduled automated task for this, we
want to make sure that it is connected
to your Google Drive because that way we
can keep everything in one centralized
location. So, if you want to create a
specific Google Drive folder where you
would like all of your content for
YouTube, for example, to be managed,
then just create the Google Drive folder
and then you want to click share.
anyone with the link can access it and
copy it. And now whenever you're asking
for certain things, you can specifically
ask it to use this. So place
all of my content moving forward in this
folder here.
Right? So I've noted it going forward.
I'll save all content into this folder.
Done.
Now, how do you make sure that that
happens? What you want to do is make
sure that you've got your Google Drive
connected,
customize,
connectors,
and then you'll be able to come to
browse connectors and Google Drive will
be there. Otherwise, if you come over
and look at mine, you can see based on
what's already connected,
Google calendar, Google Drive. I could
disconnect it, reconnect it, but you
just have to connect it. And to connect
it, if you were to add any connector,
for example, like Slack, you just click
it and you click connect. You'll be able
to click that beside Google Drive. Now,
the most important thing
is that you have this to always allow.
Now, my team has some quirks here
because of how we run our business, but
the way that you usually want it is
always allow. Done. Now you can see
everything is going to be put in that
folder moving forward. And lastly, what
we need to do,
if we come back here,
is we need to make sure we've built our
skill, we've connected to Google Drive,
and now we need to build a scheduled
task, a repeat routine that runs
automatically for you. So that for
example, every week at a certain time,
maybe you want Monday at 8:00 a.m., it's
just going to deliver your content ideas
of what you need to do that week for
you. Okay. So, how do we automate that
task? Well, we come back to our project
and you can do it a couple different
ways. You can either a simply ask it to
create, for example,
we could do it like this. Every Monday
at 7 am create a simply weekly content
plan for me. Right? Use my realtor
business profile. And maybe you want
Instagram res ideas, YouTube video
topics, and a newsletter topic. Make it
simple. This would go ahead and because
you asked for a repeat process at 7 a.m.
Claude knows that you're asking for a
scheduled task. So, you could do it
there. Or you could come down here
and click that you want a scheduled task
and say weekly
content ideas.
And now you can say every morning at or
maybe every Monday morning 7 a.m. create
a simple content plan. Use my business
profile content instructions. and you
just want it to skip all approvals so
that it actually runs autonomously and
doesn't continue to ask you for
approvals and frequency can be manual or
hourly or whatever you want but you can
just leave it as manual
and then save.
So now you've got a scheduled task here
as we can see. So this is going to be
weekly content is active every Monday
it's going to do this. We can run it now
to show you what this looks like. And
it'll populate down here and say, "Okay,
let's look at what this is going to show
us." As we can see here, it wants to
begin the process.
So, what it's going to do, and we'll let
it run for a couple seconds here so I
can show you the output of what happens.
And this is just going to show up every
single week autonomously for your
business. Now, while it's going through
that,
I want to show you that you can also
have, for example, daily briefings,
right? If we look at this, here's a
daily briefing from my business where
this is connected to my email. It's also
connected to my calendar. So, that it
just tells me every single day, good
morning. Here's your briefing for July
10th. Here's,
you know, today's schedule because it's
connected to my calendar. Here's the top
priorities and to-dos. Here's the emails
received in the last 24 hours. And then
here's the ones that need attention. The
inbox is organized. Everything is done
and good to go. Right? So, I just wanted
to show you some context as to what that
looks like. Now, let's go ahead wait for
this to finish, which is done. And we
can say, "Okay, done. This week's plan
is filmed and ready to shoot." And we
can see here
five in Instagram reels specific to our
market, Austin.
Here's the exact Instagram reel ideas
using our YouTube content plan. Right?
Here's our video ideas as well. And
here's a newsletter topic. So, two
YouTube videos for the week, one email
newsletter topic, and then five
Instagram real ideas. And this would
just automatically show up every single
Monday at 7 a.m. here under scheduled
tasks. And if you want to go back and
look at
anything else, you can come back here to
scheduled. We can see weekly content
ideas.
And that's here.
Now,
what we've done is we've built
everything out. So now, six blocks, one
assistant. We have one content
assistant. Context teaches Claude about
you. Instructions guides how it
responds. Projects organizes the work.
Skills repeat your process. Connect feed
it your files and schedule. Keep it
consistent so that your business starts
to run autonomously. That's the power of
Claude Co-work. Right now, again, my
recommendation if you want to go to the
next level is to access that free course
because this is just the surface where
things get really interesting is when
you come over to plugins. And you can
see here from my Realtor YouTube system,
it's got 16 skills built into it that
all take care of your analytics to give
you performance feedback and tell you
why you're not generating leads and
exactly how to do so. all of your ideas,
all of your SEO, scripting the videos,
repurposing it for short form,
identifying viral outliers and
everything. So again, if you want access
to our entire Claude system, you can
feel free to like the video, drop a
comment below, and we will send it to
you. But otherwise, now you have a
project with a YouTube assistant that
knows your market, you've got a
scheduled task, and you've built that a
skill. So, if you want to go,
you know, create this week's video
topics for me,
as you can see here,
working on it and it's going to be
handled by the workflow. It ran the
skill. It knows that it wants the
YouTube ideiation skill and it's going
to build it out for you. So, now you
don't have to go explain all the things
you want. You simply ask for the videos
and you can just say just this week,
right?
And then we can just click continue
and it's going to work on everything for
you using claude co-work right running
the skills using everything you need and
it's going to build out all of your
content. So that's why I love using
skills instead of trying to map
everything out over and over and over.
It knows everything for you. So, let me
just show you what this looks like.
Okay, so as you can see here now, we've
got the exact videos that we need,
everything specific to our business, and
we're good to go just by asking it to
create this week's videos. So, that's
how to properly use Claude Co-work. Set
it up, get everything dialed in with
your contacts, and now your assistant is
live and you can plug it into your
business. Now, if you want to properly
understand all the different features of
Claude, from skills to plugins to
connectors and how to automate your
business, replace virtual assistant,
check out this next video where I walk
you through everything in detail so you
have a proper understanding of how to
use Claude to turbocharge your real
estate business.